幕雨字幕组原创翻译
翻译：Brynt&超威闫叔
校对：Brynt&超威闫叔
时间轴：花格子神尼&拜仁小攀
后期：Brynt
水漾青春
给  宝贝  喝点果汁
Here you go, honey.
今天感觉如何
You all right?
有点僵硬
Quite stiff.
- 你的腿吗  - 对
- What, your leg? - Yeah.
我来给你看看
Let's have a look.
是这儿吗
Where, up here?
- 另一条腿呢  - 也有一点
- How's the other one? - Yeah.
那只腿也给我
Come on.
- 好了  - 谢了  爸
- OK. - Thanks, Dad.
对  就是这样  都喝下去  我先去换衣服  待会儿再见
Right,drink up.I'll go get dressed.See you in a minute.
琳赛  琳赛  快下来
Lindsey. Lindsey. Come on.
- 爱你  宝贝  - 我也爱你
- I love you, darling. - I love you, too.
好了  我们先试着倒立起来  然后再转移自己的重心
All right,let's start with some kick up hands-
tands,then we'll move onto some weights,yeah?
要让你自己的力量撑起身体
We're going to work on your strength, so
双手触地  将肩膀的重心集中到指尖
hands down, shoulders over fingertips...
先抬起一条腿
Kick one leg up.
好了  琳赛  另一条腿  对  就是这样  脚趾并拢
That's you. Another leg, Lindsey, that's it. Toes together,
肩膀抬高
push up through the shoulders...
就是这样  现在换你自己一个人试试
That's it. Now try it on your own.
靠你自身的力量  做得好  漂亮
Try it on your own. Good girl. Good girl!
好了  琳赛  我想看你做一次空中旋转一周半
All right, Lindsey, I want to see a back one-and-a-half twister.
别忘了我给你说的  注意你的脚跟平衡性...  非常好
Remember the things we've talked
about, your feet, your poise...That's it.
很好  动作再利落一点
That's it. A bit straighter.
好了  双臂再收拢一点
OK. I want you to think about fast arms and a tight tuck.
头别往后仰  朝前倾一点  还有  双臂再夹紧一点
Your head's going back,you need to keep
it  forwards, yeah, and a tighter tuck.
集中精力  琳赛  我知道这很辛苦
Come on, concentrate. I know it's tough, Lindsey, but it's going to
但你要是想参加12年伦敦奥运会的话以后会更难
get tougher if you want to be in contention for the Olympics in 2012.
好了  集中注意力  准备起跳
OK, focus. Here we go.
非常好  琳赛  果然不负我所望
Great, Lindsey, that's what I'm looking for.
以后也要像刚才那样练习  知道吗
Let's do some more like that, yeah?
非常棒  做得很好
Fantastic. Good work.
好了  准备好了吗
OK, are you ready?
很好  记住了  身体别往后仰
That's it. Remember, don't lean back.
比刚才还要棒  琳赛  真的  你就要达到顶尖水准了
That was much better. Really good. Lindsey, you're really getting there.
我太废了
I was rubbish.
我上二头肌跟肩胛骨之间那块肌肉拉伤了
There's a strain in my shoulder between
my upper bicep and my scapula.
这就意味着我参加奥运会的机会越来越渺茫了
It means I'm pulling back on the point of entry.
我得把这事儿解决好
I need to sort it out.
这些箱子是用来干嘛的
What are these boxes for?
我不怪你妈妈
I don't blame your mum.
我们暂时只是...
For a while now, we've just been...
我们...
We've been...
只是...
just...
人生只有一次  宝贝
You only get one life, darling,
生活也并不总能如你所愿
and things don't always go the way that you want them to go.
我从来都不想...
I never wanted to...
让你这样失望的
be letting you down like this.
我...我是失败了
I... I failed.
但是人生不如意十之八九
But that's real life, people fail sometimes.
我很对不起你
I'm sorry.
即使你失败了  你也不应该逃避
Just because you've failed doesn't mean you have to walk away.
事情没那么容易  宝贝  我真的很抱歉
It's not as simple as that, darling, I'm sorry.
这是给你的  里面有一百块钱
That's for you. It's a hundred.
他给了你多少钱
How much did he give YOU?
- 一百英镑  - 比给我的多多了
- Hundred pound. - More than he gave me.
还有个惊喜等着你呢
It's not the last surprise you're going to get today.
自己进去看吧
Take a look inside.
宝贝  这是盖瑞
Sweetheart, this is Gary.
各位  早上好
Morning, everyone.
早上好  老师
Morning, sir.
首先呢  我有个好消息要告诉大家
First, um, a good, positive piece of news.
昨天进入到镇体育队的人请站起来  大家鼓掌
All those who were in the town sports yesterday,
please stand up.Give them a round of applause.
做得很好  各位
Well done, everyone.
先取出安全套...
Take the condom out...
先看一下  别弄反了  不然你是套不上去的
Have a look at it and make sure it's the right way
up - you do not put this on the wrong way round.
你们自然会知道怎样套才是正确的
You'll know it's the right way up
因为只有正确的方式才能翻得下去
cos it can only roll down one way.
要是你拿反了的话  你是翻不下去的
If you put it on the wrong way,it won't roll down.
我们先挑一个模型  杰克  你来挑一个颜色
And we're going to choose a demonstrator. Jack, pick a colour.
- 蓝色的  - 好  蓝色的
- Blue? - Blue it is.
我们有各种颜色的  不是吗
They come in all colours, OK?
再说了  这些只是模型  不是真的阴茎
And these are demonstrators. It's not a penis.
这是拿来给你们做试验用的  知道吗
It is designed for you to practise putting condoms on, OK?
在你们翻下去之前  得先挤一下这个小囊
So before you start rolling it down, you squeeze this end bit.
确保里面没有多余的空气
Make sure there's no air trapped in there.
有谁能告诉我为什么这个这么重要吗
Can someone tell me why that's important?
- 卢克  你来说  - 要是不排净的话会很容易破的
- Luke? - It could easily break.
囊内留有空气会增加破裂几率  你们可不想这种事发生
Yeah,it increases the chance of that splitting and you don't want that to happen.
然后你们捏住头  很容易就能翻到底
So you're holding onto the end and
then simply roll it down to the base,
一定要确保所有步骤都做到位  很容易就搞定了
ensuring that it's all the way down.Nice and easy.
好了  接下来你们照着我给你们的单子一次一人练习
OK, so now you're working one at a time
and I want you ticking off on this sheet.
艾米丽  安博  你们俩在听我讲课吗
So Emily, Amber, are you listening?
好了  你们俩谁先来
So who's going first?
那艾米丽  你先  安博  你就负责核对单子上的步骤
Emily's going first. Amber, you check off on that sheet.
你先把她的名字写上  她做你就核对
You put her name on it,you check off as she goes.
名字写在“姓名”一栏
Where it says "name here".
你就把“扎克”  你的名字写在这儿
So put "Zach" and you're going to put your name there.
还有那儿
And there.
你先照着做  艾米给你打成绩
You're going to do it,and Amy's grading you.
- 早上好  老师  - 下午好  海莉  琳赛
- Morning, sir. - Afternoon, Hailey. Lindsey.
他耳朵总是红的  真是有趣
He always goes bright red,it's so funny.
你今晚去果园吗
Are you going to the grove tonight?
对  当然要去
Oh, yes!
你肯定又要去泳池了
No doubt you'll be at the pool again.
谁知道呢
You never know.
你可是琳赛・麦克卡莱姆啊
Oh, Lindsey McCallum!
我之前可没见过你打扮得这么隆重呢
I don't think I've seen you so dressed up before.
化妆之后很漂亮呢  对吧
Make-up suits you, you know?
今天的训练如何
How was training today?
很好
Fine.
对了  对了
Here. Here.
拿着
Take this.
那个...呃...
So, er,
- 你什么时候回来  - 我也不知道
- what time will you be back? - I don't know.
- 那十点钟你觉得会不会太早  - 不会
- Do you think ten o'clock's too early? - No.
要是你要回来的晚一点  记得给我们打电话  好吗
You'll give us a ring, won't you, if you're going to be later?
嗯
Mm-hm.
你确定不需要盖瑞载你一程
Are you sure you don't want Gary to give you a lift?
我确定肯定以及一定  我不想要盖瑞送我去
I'm completely sure I don't want Gary to give me a lift.
琳赛...
Lindsey...
我跟你爸两个
We had no idea,
我们真没办法过下去了
me and your dad.
我从中学到唯一一件事
If I've learnt anything at all about anything,
那就是世事难料
it's that you never know what's going to happen,ever.
还有...你今天真的...很漂亮
Hey, you look... you look lovely, by the way.
我是要去找两卷大麻还是怎么着
Am I going to get two on my spliff or what?
- 诶  诶  - 你还好吗
- Oi, oi! - You all right?
等等  酒呢
Hold on, where's the drink?!
你可不能空着手过来
You can't come down here with no drink!
你已经都喝醉了
You're loaded!
他每次都是这样
Every single time, that is.
各位  这位是琳赛
Everybody, this is Lindsey.
- 你好吗  - 好了  我来给你介绍一下  这是拉兹
- You all right? - Right, I'll start.Lindsey, this is Raz.
很高兴认识你
Nice to meet you.
还有我闺蜜  特瑞希
And my girl Tracey.
- 然后这个是卡尔  - 你很漂亮
- And then we've got Carl. - Sweet.
我们给他取了个外号叫“约克郡狸”  这家伙是戴格西
We call him Yorkie sometimes, not always. Degsie.
- 你好  - 他是个酷酷的京吉人
- Hello. - He's a cool ginge!
那边那俩是克莱尔跟我死党桑塔娜
And then we've got Claire and my girl Santana down there.
这就是全体成员了
So that's all the crew.
你想喝一杯吗  小公主
Do you want a drink then, princess?
不用了  谢谢
Oh, no, thank you.
小公主  怎么  你难道是想打动她的芳心吗
Princess! What, is that a move or something?!
闭嘴
Shut up!
- 他追过我 但没有得逞  - 告诉...他告诉过我那是什么意思
- He tried it on me but it didn't work. - Tell the...He told me what's mean.
那你想抽烟吗  你想来一根吗  小公主
Do you want a smoke then, do you want a smoke, princess?
- 不用了  谢谢  - 你确定
- No, ta. - Are you sure?
这可是个好东西
It's good shit, this, you know.
你让查理试过吗
Did you get it off Charlie?
你们看起来就跟一群嫖客一样  各位
You look like a bunch of kerb crawlers from back there, people!
你还好吗  戴格斯
You all right, Degs?
最近如何  老兄
How you getting on, mate?
卡尔  过得如何  拉兹
Carl. How's it going, Raz?
简直不可思议  对吧
Hardly to believe it, isn't it?
天气真是适合聚会啊
What lovely weather for it!
你真是公主吗
Are you a princess?
- 不是  - 那就好  我叫罗柏
- No! - Cool. I'm Rob.
我知道  我叫琳赛
I know. I'm Lindsey.
你要去惠顿对吗
You go to Whetton, don't you?
没错
I do, yeah.
嗯  我看得出来
Yeah, I recognise you.
你是游泳运动员还是什么
You're a swimmer or summat, aren't you?
- 跳水运动员  - 那就对了
- A diver. Yeah. - That's it.
你已经收获了很多证书奖章还有奖品  对吧
You've won loads of certificates and medals and awards, ain't you?
哇哦
Wow.
我以前怎么从没在这附近见过你
I ain't seen you down here before.
我以前没来过这儿
I've not been here before.
- 那你是从哪儿来的  - 金斯索普上城区
- Where you from? - Up Kingsthorpe.
我知道  那地方每层楼都有间浴室
Oh, yeah, every house has got a bathroom on each floor,
主人的房间就在起居室正上方  你肯定还有个车库
master bedroom's above the living room, you've got a garage,
还有个漂亮的小花园
nice little garden set up.
你是怎么知道的
How did you know that?
你跟你父母住一块儿吗
Do you live with mum and dad?
我跟我妈
With my mum.
还有我小弟住一起
And my little brother.
好吧  那他几岁了
Oh aye, how old's he?
十岁
Ten.
那他肯定是个彻头彻尾的小混蛋
Is he a complete and total wank
of a pain in the jacksy then, yeah?
- 不  他不是那样的    - 不是吗
- No, he's not. -  Nah?
不是  他人挺好的
No, he's great.
我有事想跟你说  琳
Can I tell you something, Linds?
说吧
Yeah.
我觉得你实在是太美了
I think you're completely gorgeous.
琳赛  我没有保护措施
Lindsey, I've got no protection.
这是你的初夜  对吗
That was your first time, wasn't it?
嗯
Mm.
那现在该怎么办
So, what now?
现在都快半夜了
It's nearly midnight.
不用你管
No shit.
- 你妈妈很担心你  - 是吗
- Your mum was very worried. - Yeah?
是的  你明天还得上课呢
Yeah. You've got school tomorrow.
琳赛  听我说  呃...
Lindsey, look, er...
我...
I'm...
我不是你爸爸
I'm not your dad.
这点我很清楚
I know that.
我也不会装作我是  好吗
Look, I'm not going to pretend that I am, OK?
可是我真的很爱你妈妈
But I love your mum very much.
但要是你半夜才会回家
And,you know,if you're going to come in at midnight,
你就给她打给电话  让她知道你平安就好
if you could just, you know, give her
a call, let her know where you are.
她真的非常担心你的安危  琳赛
You know,she was worried sick about you,Lindsey.
说完了  那就晚安吧
Good. Night-night.
你越来越棒了  琳赛  刚才那个摆肩做得非常好
That's much more like it, Lindsey, that's
a good rolling of the shoulders, yeah?
要有力地长划  记得吗  做得很好
Good long strokes, remember? Good girl.
你好
Hiya.
琳
Linds.
你今晚还去果园吗
Are you going to the grove tonight?
也许吧
Probably.
我要去
Cos I am.
很好
Cool.
那我们就在那儿再见  行吗
Well, I'm going to see you there then, aren't I?
在男性蛋蛋下面有一个区域...
There's an area just underneath where the balls are.
你确定你真想听吗
Are you sure you want to hear this?!
我确定
I do, yeah.
这不像你的风格  你知道我什么意思吗  好吧
It's just not very you,do you know what I mean? OK. So...
当你添下去的时候...
When you go down on them right...
提醒你一下  有些人的会尝起来怪怪的
Some of them can taste a bit funny, by the way.
怪怪的
Funny?
不是所有人啦  只是一部分而已
Well, not all of them. Some are all right.
那那部分人占的比例是多少
Like, what percentage?
呃  我也不清楚  大概是5:5吧
Er, I don't know. Maybe 50/50?
也可能是4:6
40/60?
管它呢
Anyway.
当他们快要到了...
When they're getting close...
- 快要到了  - 当他们快要射了的时候
- Getting close? - When they're about to come!
你就会感觉得到  因为他们身体会微颤  然后你就用手指
You can feel it cos they'll start to shake a bit. You get your finger
按住他蛋蛋跟股沟之间的位置  就能暂时阻止他射出来
and you press it just in this area between his balls
and his arse, and it stops him from coming.
这会让他那精虫上脑的头冷静一下
It will blow his fucking mind.
他要再射的话就得多花五分钟了
He'll be able to go like for about another five more minutes.
但这一次  他就会射得到处都是
And then,when he comes,it will go fucking everywhere.
我上次头发上都射得到处都是
Last time, it went in my hair.
真的假的
Really?!
当然是真的  害得我不得不洗了头发  湿漉漉地回家了
Yeah!I had to wash it.I had to go home with wet hair.
还跟我父母解释了大半天
Try explaining that one away!
我就可以说我跳水去了
I could say I'd gone diving.
你这周末准备干吗
What are you doing this weekend?
什么
What?
你~这~个~周~末~准~备~干~嘛
What are you doing this weekend?
怎么这么问
Why?
因为我周末没有安排
Cos I'm not doing anything.
呃... 琳...天呐...嗯...
Aw, Linds, man, um...
我现在真的很不想交女朋友
I don't really do girlfriends and shit.
我觉得这样没什么用
I'm just a bit wank at them.
琳
Linds!
- 今晚去果园  你去吗  - 我要训练
- Grove tonight, you coming? - I'm training.
- 我要早点过去  - 我要训练
- I'm getting there early. - I'm training.
- 真丢人  老兄  真丢人  - 哦  不
- Woah! Shame, mate, shame! - Oh! Oh, no!
兄弟们  我们得快点出去  快点   赶快出去  快
Boys, boys, out of here, quick time.
Get out of here, quick time!
就是这样  琳赛  这就是我们想要的效果  对吧
That's the one, Lindsey,that's exactly
what we've been talking about, yeah?
你自己一定感觉到了
You must have felt it yourself.
双腿夹得很紧  身体控制得也非常棒
Your feet were tight,your body was controlled.
这就是评委想看到的东西  你说对吗
That's exactly the things the judges are looking for, yeah?
他们要来水晶宫了
They're coming to Crystal Palace.
英国国家游泳队要来了
British Swimming.
他们要为奥运会选拔运动员
They're making selections for the Olympic team.
我们能换个时间再聊吗
Can we do another hour?
其他人还有多少要去  琳
How many other kids are going, Linds?
没了  就我一个人
There are no other kids. I'm the only one.
不错嘛  琳
That's great, Linds.
你是说要去伦敦吗
London, did you say?
宝贝  我不知道该怎么做
Sweetheart, I don't know what to do.
听着  我不能不去工作
Look, I can't get off work.
目前家里情况也很困难
It's really hard at the moment.
我们会想办法的
We'll think of something.
想什么办法
Like what?
我可以送你去
I could take you.
我不想让你送我
I don't want you to take me.
这又跟你有毛关系啊
What's it got to do with you?
关你娘的鸟事
It's none of your fucking business.
嘿  琳赛
Hey! Lindsey!
诶  琳赛
Oi! Lindsey!
他是个好男人  你知道吗
He's a very kind man, you know?
他是真的在乎我
He cares about me.
他也能让我感觉到幸福
He makes me happy.
每次跟他在一起我心里都很开心
I even catch myself laughing.
好几次我甚至都笑出了声
Out loud, sometimes.
大多数时候  他仿佛非常了解我的心思
You know, half of the time, it's like he knows what I'm thinking.
我们可以坐在一块聊上好几个小时
We can be in the same room and not have
to talk to one another for hours.
而且每次出去时他都会挽着我的手
He holds my hand when I'm out with him.
你在这儿干嘛呢
What are you doing here?
我想跟你说会儿话
I wanted to talk to you.
琳  我都在这儿等了你一个小时了
Linds, I've been waiting for an hour!
我以前从来没有等过别人这么久  琳赛
I've not waited an hour for anybody before,Lindsey.
你知道我要上多少课吗
Do you know how many lessons I've had?
2500堂
2,500.
那可是足足一万个小时
That's 10,000 hours.
整整420天  一年零三个月我都得待在泳池里面
420 days.A year and a quarter in a pool.
你知道那么长时间我可以做多少其它事儿吗
Do you have any idea what else I
could have been doing with that time?
我现在才不会半途而废呢
I'm not going to throw that away now.
没人让你半途而废  琳
No one's asking you to, Linds.
不会有人让你退出的
At all.
觉得我跳得怎么样
How was that?
还不错
It was all right.
但我见过跳得更好的
Seen better.
谢了  大混蛋
Thanks, arsehole!
在那上面跳如何
What's up with that one?
- 哪个  - 那个木板
- You what? - That board.
- 你想让我在那上面跳  - 对
- What, you want me to do that? - Yeah.
不去  去你丫的
No, you can fuck off!
我才不会在刚跳完就去跳那个
I'm not doing that after that!
来呀  让我看看你有什么能耐
Go on, let's see what YOU can do, then.
哦~  到我这儿来
Ohh, come here.
不许赢我
Don't knock me down.
快出来吧
You, come on. Just come out here.
- 我觉得这样太缺德了  琳  - 是吗
- I thought that was wicked, Linds. - Yeah?
是的  你居然还觉得这样做很好
Thought that was proper, yeah.
谢了  你个笨蛋
Well, thank you, you clown.
不用谢
It's all right.
那你就让我看看你的能耐
Let's see what you can do, then.
你害怕了吗
Are you scared, yeah?
- 对  - 快跳吧
- Yeah. - Go on.
好了  把头含起来
Right, OK. Tuck your head in.
- 现在把双手抬起来  好吗  - 行
- Now put your arms up. Yeah? - Yeah.
你跳水之前得预想一下
You've got to visualise the dive before you do it.
什么
What?!
- 你得先知道  - 别管我
- You've got to know - Leave alone with me,
- 你要怎么跳  - 让我自己跳
- what you're going to do, -  leave me alone.
你头脑里先得要想一下待会儿要怎么跳
you've got to know what you're going to do in your head.
- 知道了  - 那就这样吧
- OK. - All right then.
- 好吧  - 好吧
- All right. - All right.
- 我不行  - 你当然行  跳吧
- I can't! - Yeah, you can! Go on!
对  我跳
Right, go on.
你一定要先想好该怎么跳
You've got to visualise what you're going to do.
就在你脑中想像一下...  别
Like, just think about it in your head... No!
我好像感觉被灼伤了
I feel like I've got sunburn.
放屁
That was shit!
- 简直是在胡闹  - 我这一跳可是奥运会水准
- Crock of shit. - Well, mine's Olympic standard.
- 你说什么  - 拉我一把
- You what? - Give us a hand up.
你这个蠢货
You prick.
- 什么  - 你这个蠢货
- What?! - You prick!
居然敢把我拉下水
For pushing me in the water.
你不是自己掉下来的么
Did you not just fall in?
这池子有点深
It's quite deep.
- 池子好深啊  - 你怕了
- It's quite deep. - You scared?
好了  你已经到岸边了
That's it, you're nearly at the side.
我们应该去儿童泳池吗
Shall we go in the baby pool?
- 你好 特瑞希  - 你跟罗柏在一起干嘛
- Hiya, Tracey. - What you doing with Robert?
什么
What?
你跟罗柏搅在一起干嘛
What you doing with Robert?
我在问你话呢
I asked you a question!
你到底跟罗柏在一起干什么
What have you been doing with Robert?
- 没干嘛  - 没听见
- Nowt. - Sorry?!
我们什么事也没有
Nothing.
骗子
Liar.
你妈的大骗子
You fucking liar.
不许跟我撒谎
Don't lie to me!
你就打算一直站在那儿吗
So you just going to stand there?
你知道吗  我最受不了你这种女孩了  你真是可悲
Do you know what, I can't stand girls like you, you're pathetic.
你这个淫贱的荡妇
You're a dirty little slag.
你究竟跟罗柏在一起干嘛
What are you doing with Robert?
我再问你最后一次  你到底跟罗柏在一起干什么
I'm going to ask you one more time,
what are you doing with Robert?!
好了  琳赛  都缝好了
OK, Lindsey, that's all done now.
你只要保持伤口的清洁  应该就不会结疤了
What I need you to do is keep that nice
and clean and it'll heal beautifully.
我这样还能游泳吗
Will I be able to swim with it?
当然可以
I don't see why not.
你下周还得再过来一次  好让护士帮你拆线
You need to make an appointment for next week so
that the nurse can take the stitches out for you.
都弄好了  你觉得如何
All done. Is that OK?
你还好吗
You all right?
我还有件事
There was something else.
什么事
What's that?
我有个地方总是有血迹
There was some bleeding.
在哪儿
What kind of bleeding?
- 我内裤那块儿  - 好吧
- In my knickers. - OK.
你开始来月经了吗  琳赛
Have you started your periods yet, Lindsey?
是吗  规律吗
Yes? Regular?
- 但你觉得这次来得不寻常是吗  - 对
- So this is a bit unusual for you,is it?Yeah?- Yeah.
琳赛  宝贝  你觉得有没有可能你是怀孕了
Lindsey, sweetheart, do you think you might be pregnant?
不是很确定吗
Not very sure?
好吧  我们可以做个检查  就做个尿检就行
OK, we can do a test, it's just a urine test.
不会耽搁太久的
Won't take very long.
你觉得行吗
Will that be all right?
还是心里有个数好些
Probably better to know.
我给你个杯子  你待会儿就尿在里面  我们会检测出来的
I'll just go and get a pot and then you can
do a wee for me and we can sort that out.
我去去就回
Back in a minute.
- 你迟到了  - 我知道
- You're late. - Yeah.
注意  双臂打直
Look, line up.
对  就是这样  再压紧一点
That's it, that's it. Really squeeze.
用力挤  非常好
Really squeeze, that's great.
做得很好  现在放松  可以了
Well done. And relax, that's enough.
你可以先休息会儿了   刚才做的非常好
You can stop now. That's good.
可以停了  琳赛
You can stop now, Lindsey.
够了
That's enough.
我说“够了”
入水水花太大
That was a sloppy entrance.
还不够好  你是把自己抛下去的
Not good enough. You just gave up.
我想看你再来一次  你的脚打水太严重了  你的...
I want to see it again.Your feet were sloppy,your...
嘿  回来  回来  回来听我说完
Hey,come here,come here!Come here and speak to me.
我跟你说话的时候不许扭头就走  你心不在焉的
Don't you walk away from me when I'm
speaking to you. You weren't focused.
你得再用功一点
You have to concentrate more.
我认为我们需要在每周多加四个小时时间训练
I think we need to put in four more hours a week.
嘿
Hey.
看着我
Look at me.
琳赛  看着我的眼睛  这就是你得付出的
Lindsey, look at me. This is what's involved.
这就是代价  宝贝
This is what it takes, sweetheart.
要是你想在接下来两年内挖掘出你的潜力
If you want to take this as far as
you've got the potential to take it
那你就得习惯像蒸汽机一样努力的工作
in the next two years,then you've got to
get used to working like a steam train.
知道吗
Yeah?
你到底还想不想去  琳赛
Do you think you're up for it, Lindsey?
要是你不想的话就告诉我  我马上打给国家游泳泳队
Because if you're not,tell me now and
I'll ring British Swimming straight away.
我不想浪费我的时间  宝贝
I don't want to waste my time, sweetheart.
把手搭在别人肩上什么的
I'm shit at this kind of thing.
我最不在行了
The whole arm round the shoulders bit.
但是我知道这些对你来说很艰难
But I do know things have been tough for you.
我确实也理解
I do understand that.
但我觉得你要是把这次机会放跑了
I just think that if you blow this opportunity now,
你会后悔一辈子的
you're going to regret it for the rest of your life.
你觉得呢
Yeah?
是罗柏的吗
Was it Robert?
罗柏・韦斯利  你到底在想什么啊
Robert Wisley, what were you thinking?!
你告诉他了吗
Have you told him yet?
你觉得他会怎么说
What do you think he'll say?
听着  这句话我只说一次  知道吗
Look, I'm only going to say this once, yeah?
这当然还得看你自己的决定
This is a decision that is absolutely up to you.
但你自己也知道  现在它还只是一个化学物的集合体
But you do know, don't you, that at the minute,
it's not much more than a collection of chemicals.
甚至都还没有成形
It doesn't even have a body, even.
这样说好像不合适
Not properly.
它现在甚至比乐高的商标都还小
It's smaller than one of them little Lego figures.
要是你现在做流产的话  对你身体也不会有什么影响的
If you wanted an abortion, it wouldn't hurt you,
也不会影响你以后再要孩子
it wouldn't damage you and it wouldn't stop
you from having a baby later on in life,
你要是准备好了就告诉我
say when you're more ready to.
你懂我的意思对吧
Do you know what I mean?
你有心事对吗
You got something going on in your head?
- 没有啊  - 你绝对有
- No. - Yeah, you have.
- 我真没有  - 你肯定有
- I haven't. - Yeah, you have.
你说话的时候眼睛朝左看了
You looked to the left.
你朝右看就是在思考  朝左就是在说谎  你刚才就朝左看了
If you look to the right, you're thinking, you look
to the left, you're lying. You looked to the left.
我发现...
I found out...
呃...  嗯...
Er, erm,
我下周可能要去伦敦
I might be going to London next week.
那儿有一场国际竞赛  而且还有
There's a national competition and there's going to be
国家游泳队的代表队  他们可以决定
a representative from British Swimming there
我是否能进队为12年的奥运会备战
who'll decide if I can go onto the next stage of training for 2012.
什么  奥运会吗
What, the Olympics?
- 为奥运会备战  对  - 去他大爷的
- For the Olympics, yeah. - Fucking hell!
嗯
Yeah.
难怪你那么痛苦了
Well, no wonder you're so miserable, then.
- 什么  - 去他娘的奥运会  那是什么鸟玩意儿
- What?!- Well,the fucking Olympics.How shit is that?
去你大爷的
Fuck you!
来吧
Come on.
- 干嘛  - 我要进去了
- What?! - I'm getting in.
- 你什么  - 你怎么还没脱
- You what? - You are an' all.
- 把衣服脱了  - 我泳衣都没带呢
- Get your clothes off. - I ain't got my kit.
我们得搞快点  要你那套装备干嘛  我们可是在海里游
We've got to be quick.What do you need your kit for? We're in the sea.
好吧
Oh, all right!
脱吧  都脱掉
Take it off. Straight in.
- 天呐  - 对  就是这样  不错嘛
- Oh, my God! - Yes, well played!
你什么时候定的票
What time did you book it for?
十五分钟前
Quarter past.
给  我给你买了这个
Here, I got this for you.
- 这是用来补充葡萄糖的  - 谢了
- It's for the glucose. - Thanks.
再见
See ya.
嘿  来抱抱
Hey. Come here!
我真为你骄傲
Oh, I'm proud of you.
一路顺风  好吗
Good luck, all right?
- 祝你好运   - 也祝你好运
- Good luck. - Good luck.
你到了记得打电话给我们  好吗
You'll give us a ring, won't you?
- 知道  - 嗯
- Yeah. - Yeah.
嘿  好好玩儿
Hey. Enjoy yourself.
一定要赢啊  知道吗
Just win, yeah?
- 嗯  - 再见  狗头姐
- Yeah. - See you later, monghead!
- 再见  口臭弟  - 琳赛...
- See you later, bad breath. - Lindsey...
我真的很爱你
I really love you.
好吧
OK.
- 我得出发了  - 你一定要打电话回来  好吗
- I've got to go. - You'll ring me, yes?
好
Yep.
诶  真是太尴尬了
Blimey. How embarrassing was that?
走吧  去吃点早餐
Come on. Let's get some breakfast.
做得好  就该这样
Well done! That's the one!
真是完美的一跃  干得漂亮
That was a beautiful pike. Well done!
你太棒了  宝贝  我真为你感到骄傲
You were so good! I'm so proud of you, darling.
真的  哈~
Really. Huh?
接下来你们要怎么做
So what happens next?
他们会跟艾莉森联系  告诉她制度的实施
They'll contact Alison about implementing the regime.
嗯哼
Mm-hm.
但她还是会继续做你教练的  对吧
And she's going to keep training you, isn't she?
这不是件好事吗  你说呢
Well, that's good, isn't it?
是吗
Yeah?
我几周后就会找好公寓
I get my flat in a few weeks.
你跟麦迪可以过来玩儿  我会带你们参观的
You and Matty can come up come
and visit, I'll show you around.
三分之二个IPod3
Two thirds of an iPod Nano.
什么
What?
一些好点的Top Shop的衣服
Some quite nice dresses from Top Shop.
十张CD唱片  一台完好的DVD播放机
Ten CDs. An all right DVD player.
你在说什么呢  宝贝
What you talking about, darling?
你那一百英镑能买的十件东西
Things you can buy for a hundred quid.
- 宝贝...  - 一百英镑
- Darling... - A hundred pound.
不...
No...
我不知道该怎么说那件事
I don't know what to say about that.
你可不是不知道吗
No, you don't, do ya?
听我说  宝贝  琳赛...
Look, darling, Lindsey...
听我说  爱...
Listen, love...
听我说  我对我犯的错真的很抱歉  用了错误的方式
Listen,I'm really sorry.I know that was the wrong
thing to do, the wrong way to go about it.
人经常会犯傻的  不是吗
People do silly things, OK?
我真不知道该如何是好
I don't know how to do this stuff.
我很爱你  宝贝
I love you, darling.
拜托你不要让我跟你妈的事影响到我们的关系
Please don't let this get in the way
of us, and really don't let it get
也不要影响到你的事业  因为你现在做的非常了不起
in the way of what you're doing,cos you're doing so brilliant.
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
我他娘的怀孕了
I'm fucking pregnant.
不  琳赛  琳赛...
No! Lindsey! Lindsey...
宝贝
Darling!
拜托  宝贝
Please, babe.
琳
Linds?
罗柏...
Robert...
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
我没跟你开玩笑  罗柏
This is serious, Robert.
这  我们  我...
This, us, me...
我怀孕了  这是真的  我真的怀孕了  是你的孩子
I'm pregnant! It's real, it's happening, it's yours!
你得负责任
You need to get your head around it.
我只是有点吓着了  琳赛
I'm just a bit scared, Lindsey.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
- 你到底干了什么好事  - 别这样  老爸
- What have you done? - Don't, Dad.
罗柏  你到底知不知道你妈离开后我工作有多难吗
Robert, have you any idea how hard I've
worked for you since your mother left?!
要一个人操持这个家
Kept all this together,
而你就是这样帮我的
and this is you just shitting on it.
我想回去
I want to come back.
我想继续跳水
I want to go back to diving.
我看得出来  老兄  虽然你想  但还是无能为力
I can see it, mate, you ain't in control and you want to be.
谢谢观看  更多字幕请关注“幕雨字幕组”新浪微博
我不是个坏人
I'm not a bad person.
我希望我们能破镜重圆
I wanted us to be together all along.